So I think a
big part of having Colter in a lab is just spending
time with each other. And so I think if we went
and did activities together, like,
I really live pickleball.
Other people in that probably like playing pickleball.
Like, let's go play pickleball together, you
know? Something like that, just to get more interaction.
Even outside of the lab, I think, can be beneficial
for building relationships.
And maybe there can be like a,
like kind of systemize the
onboarding a little bit more.
Some people come in. And, you know, we give them
a chance to introduce themselves and we make
it very clear to them that if they need anything,
we're happy to help, you know,
simple things like that.
Yeah, some, a few ideas, but.
I think that would be good, too.
I think also,
you kind of said everything that I was thinking
in regards to AI, I guess.
I think like Sam was mentioning, we use it as
an
assistant and as a help, not as our,
like,
it's not how we do our research.
It's a help for our research use as a tool versus
the main idea. I think that kind of goes along
with what you were saying, because if we do that,
then it's not like we're only interacting on
GitHub or the meeting or, like,
pinging cloud and just having cloud to be our
only source of discussion and interaction.
Yeah, I like that reframing you and Sam talked
about with AI and being the one in
charge and using AI as an assistant versus a,
um,
uh, uh, uh, uh, being the assistant to the AI.
Um,
and then I think there's also a lot of specific
use cases where it makes a lot of sense to use
AI. Like,
instead of doing a four set,
four hours Google search session for gathering
research and compiling it, you can have it.
Dude, that's, that's a really powerful use of
AI that, um, doesn't necessarily,
I think there's a lot more benefit there than
there's, uh, than what it takes away.
Um,
versus other cases like actually writing the
paper. Yeah.
Maybe for a first draft, but I think.
makes more, there's a lot more benefit for the
user, the lab assistant to,
um, do that themselves and then have AI as an
assistant to help facilitate writing.
Um,
and so I think, I think you're totally right
with that and making that the lab culture, of
making that the understanding when people come
and this is how we use AI.
Yeah, and that helps you like get the background
to do their research because like,
it's giving you information.
It's not doing the research for you.
Like, you're not going to be publishing on what
already exists.
So I don't see any problem in using it to learn
as long as that doesn't go into,
okay, now Claude, do all this research from
all these tests, interpret it, and then do something
based off of what you learned.
I guess it's kind of what Beijing optimization
is like it learns from
past information. Mm -hmm.
That'll be a closed loop.
Yeah.
But again, like, making sure that we understand
everything that goes on and we interpret it as
well, and give our own ideas instead of,
okay, Claude, here's,
like, I don't have any ideas, just do whatever
you think is best. Maybe
making up the culture to actually put in some
effort, okay, I need to, I need to give it some
ideas that I've thought of myself.
Yeah. And then have it,
give it that, and then have it, um,
extrapolate. Yeah, have a critique your ideas.
Like, yeah,
give it a baseline. Like, here's what I'm thinking.
Is there something wrong with what I'm thinking?
How could this be improved.
And then once it gives you those, like,
criticisms,
see, okay, is what it's telling me I can do better,
actually going to make it better, or are there
problems with what I see that it's doing?
And that'll help you think as well while while
you're using AI.
Yeah, I agree.